hy-vee.com 2017-02-22

# Privacy

## Company

  * Careers
  * Scholarships
  * Sustainability
  * Mobile
  * E-mail Newsletters
  * Community
  * About Hy-Vee
  * Press Room

| 

  * Company
  * Privacy

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Hy-Vee, Inc. (“Hy-Vee”, “we”, “our” or “us”) is committed to respecting and protecting our customers’ privacy. This policy describes (a) the types of interactions with us through which we collect your personal information, (b) what type of information we collect, (c) how we use and protect your information, and (d) with whom we share your information. We take the issue of privacy very seriously and value the trust you place in us each time you visit our stores and use the services we provide.

These provisions may be changed from time to time and without notice at Hy-Vee's sole discretion and as provided by applicable law. You should check this privacy policy frequently for any such changes, but, in any case, your continued access or use of our Services shall constitute acceptance of any modifications of the privacy statement. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, we encourage you to contact us using any of the methods outlined at the end of our privacy policy.

For purposes of this privacy policy, our “Services” means any one or more, or all, of the following interactions that you may have with us: our stores, websites, promotions, loyalty and/or rewards programs, mobile applications, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, surveys, forums, customer service requests and communication. This list is not intended to be exhaustive.

## Who is Collecting the Information?

Hy-Vee collects information as outlined in this privacy policy in order to deliver the products and services that you request and to help us improve your experience with us.

## What Information Do We Collect?

 _Automatic Collection of Information:_

When you interact with our Services, our system will automatically gather and store certain information about you. Unless you are logged into your online account, this information does not identify you personally and is used in an aggregate way to help us improve our Services and tell us the number of users of our Services each day. Our Services automatically collect and record information from visitors, which includes, but is not limited to: domain name; your computer’s internet protocol address; data showing the order in which you accessed our Services; the name and release number of the web browser software you used; the operating system of the computer used; the date and time you access our Services; the address of the website that linked to our Services (referral URL); any search terms used when interacting with our Services.  If you are logged into your online account, the information that we collect identifies you personally.

In addition to the automatic collection of information set forth above, we collect data that is publically available by providing you with a single sign-on service using your third-party social networking login credentials. This includes, but is not limited to, Facebook, Google, and Twitter. This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing by providing better product recommendations or special offers that may interest you. We may also access and use available information from your third-party social network profile, such as your name, location, profile picture, profile information, gender, list of friends, friends’ profiles or postings, email addresses, wall postings and news feed. You should know that any information or content you post to a third-party site will be subject to that site’s own privacy policy.

 _Permission-based Collection of Information:_

At different places within our Services, depending upon the feature(s) you use (i.e. forum, shopping cart, locator services), you may be asked to volunteer personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, credit and/or debit card information, physical location, e-mail address, mailing address and telephone number. We also collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

## How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

The information we gather automatically and with your permission during your interaction with our Services is used in some the following ways: to monitor, review, measure and analyze website utilization; to modify and enhance our Services; to improve the content and design of our Services; to respond to your requests; to fulfill your requests or orders for our products and services; to communicate with you about your requests; to distribute news and other information; to administer surveys, promotions, giveaways, contests and sweepstakes, and loyalty and/or rewards programs; to alert you about product information and recalls; and to verify your identity. The foregoing list is not exclusive or exhaustive.

## With Whom Will the Information be Shared?

The personally identifiable information gathered during your use of our Services is shared with organizations affiliated with Hy-Vee, Inc., and with third parties through which we either fulfill your order or information request.

We will not rent, sell, exchange or provide personally identifiable information to any third-party organization without your express consent (opt-in).

We may disclose or otherwise make available information we’ve gathered during your use of our Services, including personally identifiable information, aggregate data and/or anonymous data, to service providers that assist us with our business operations, including provision of the Services. We require our service providers to keep your information secure and confidential. Our service providers may not use or disclose your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing services to us or on our behalf.

We may disclose information when the disclosure is necessary to protect the safety or the property rights of Hy-Vee, our customers, and/or our employees; when cooperating with reasonable requests from law enforcement; and when legally compelled to do so.

In connection with sweepstakes, contests, giveaways, loyalty and/or rewards programs and other types of promotional campaigns, we will post winners’ lists on our website and throughout our other advertising mediums, as well as make available winners’ lists to interested parties who may request the same in writing following the expiration of any such promotional campaign. In addition, we will provide winners’ names, addresses, telephone numbers, and if applicable social security numbers, with appropriate governmental agencies. In addition, certain promotional campaigns may require disclosure of personally identifiable information of entrants to promotional campaign participants, including but not limited to sponsors and promotional campaign administrators. If personally identifiable information is to be shared with promotional campaign participants, the rules applicable to each such promotional campaign shall disclose the fact that such information may be shared with such promotional campaign participants.

## Communication Defaults: Opt-in, Opt-out

For text message based promotions, we use an opt-in for text message communication with you. We will not communicate with you via text message without your express consent.

For all of other Services, we use an opt-out standard for email and mail communications with you. Opt-out means that your consent to our communication with you is implied, but if you request to opt-out of specific types of communications, either by unsubscribing from the specific email communication or contacting us to opt-out of specific mailed correspondence, we will cease sending them to you.

Individuals may notify us that they wish to opt-out and prevent the transfer of their personally identifiable information to organizations affiliated with Hy-Vee, Inc., or correct such information by writing to us at the contact address at the end of this privacy statement. If you opt-out we may not be able to fulfill your order or answer your information request.

## Our Use of Cookies

Many websites now use "cookies" to provide useful features to their visitors by providing customizable and personalized services. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. For example, a website may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you, your preferences or the pages you last visited. Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies, or to ask you if you would like to accept or decline a cookie from a particular site before it is set. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the Help section of the toolbar. You should know, however, that if you reject a cookie, certain functions and conveniences of a site may not work properly. We use cookies on our Services to store and sometimes track visitor information and preferences, including remembering your login information for when you return to our Services.

## Our Children's Privacy Policy

Our Services are directed towards a general audience and do not feature information and services geared towards to children 13 years and under. We do not collect personal information from anyone we know is a child under 13 without parental consent.

## Registration for Access

Some Services require you to provide some personal information through a registration process in order to take advantage of certain features and to access certain content areas. For example, a registration form might request your name, telephone number and e-mail address.

Some of the features of our Services may require registration and the disclosure of some personal information, which may include a specialized registration process for certain promotions, forums, programs and events.

## Links to Other Sites

Websites often provide a number of links that offer direct access to other useful or interesting websites holding potential value to site visitors. Inclusion of the other sites by links does not imply any endorsement of the material or information on the other sites. Users are encouraged to review the privacy policy of each linked site before sharing personal information.

This site includes links to non-affiliated external websites. We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each linked site, as we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. Please check our privacy policy periodically for changes.

## Website Contact Information

If you have questions about our privacy policy, or feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us.

Hy-Vee, Inc.  
Internet Relations  
5820 Westown Parkway  
West Des Moines, Iowa 50266

Or call our Consumer Information Line toll free at:  
1-800-289-8343  
Hours of Operation:  
9 a.m. to 4 p.m. central time Monday through Friday (except holidays).

## Modification Date

This privacy policy was last modified on, and shall be effective from and after **February 2, 2017.**

|  | Corporate Citizenship Report  
---  
  
##### [Being A Good Citizen](https://www.hy-vee.com/company/about-hy-vee/corporate-citizenship-report.aspx)

At Hy-Vee, we are uniquely positioned to lead the way in terms of sustainability and we’re focused on being proactive in this area because it’s the right thing to do.

The [2016 Corporate Citizenship Report](https://www.hy-vee.com/company/about-hy-vee/corporate-citizenship-report.aspx) details how we work to strengthen our communities and help our customers who live in them.  
  
Seasons  
---  
  
##### Helpful Products And Ideas

Hy-Vee Seasons provides you with recipes, crafts, tips and helpful seasonal information. Celebrate the seasons in your life!  
  
Midwest Heritage Bank  
---  
  
##### Online Bank

Get secure access to your accounts from any web-connected computer with Internet banking convenient online bill pay.  
  
Wedding  
---  
  
##### Hy-Vee Will Make Your Wedding An Event To Remember

If you are planning a wedding, Hy-Vee can help with beautiful flowers, magnificent cakes, amazing catering and more.
